Choral Octavos by Yale Alumni
Yale University Music Library
- David Stanley Smith
  - All Hail to the Days (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1925), 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - The Annunciation (Bas-Quercy Carol) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Translated by: Edward Bliss Reed (Arranged by D.S. Smith)
    Stainer & Bell, Ltd. (1923) 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - The Annunciation (Flemish Carol) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    English Translation by: Edward Bliss Reed (Arranged by D.S. Smith)
    Stainer & Bell, Ltd. (1938) 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - Apocalyptic Lamb (Polish Carol XVIIth Century) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    English Version by: Edward Bliss Reed (Arranged by D.S. Smith)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1929) 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - The Charming Shepherds (Besançon Carol XVIIIth Century) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Translated by Edward Bliss Reed (Arranged by D.S. Smith)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1927) 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - The Children's Carol, Saboly, Nicolas, 1614-1675 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    From the Provençal Translated by Edward Bliss Reed
    Harmonized for SATB by D.S. Smith
  - Come, Dear Brother (Franconian Folk Carol) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1926), 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - Come See a Wonder, Saboly, Nicolas, 1614-1675 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Translated from the Provençal by Edward Bliss Reed
    Harmonized from Seguin's version for SATB by D.S. Smith
    H.W. Gray Co. (1921), New York
  - Daybreak Op. 33, No. 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Part-Song for Mixed Chorus
    G. Schirmer (1917)
  - The Fallen Star Op. 26 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    For Mixed Chorus and Orchestra
    Paderewski Prize Composition, 1909
    Text: George Darley
    G. Schirmer (1910), New York
  - Go Not, Happy Day Op. 36, No. 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    For Three-part Chorus of Women's Voices
    From "Maud" by Alfred Tennyson
    G. Schirmer (1915), New York
  - He Is Born (XVIIIth Century Air de Chasse "La Tête Bizarde") (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Arranged from the version of Legeay by D.S. Smith
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1930) 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - Hush, O Earth (Franconian Carol) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - In the Darkness (Basque Carol) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    English version by Edward Bliss Reed (Arranged by D.S. Smith)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1933), 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - The Inn (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Arranged for Solo voices with accompaniment of chorus or piano by D.S. Smith
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1924), 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - The Innocents (Russian Carol) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    SATB and Organ or Piano
    English version by N.V. and Edward Bliss Reed (Arranged by D.S. Smith)
  - Jesus, You Are All Flame and Fire, Saboly, Nicolas, 1614-1675 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    French and English versions by Edward Bliss Reed
    H.W. Gray Co. (1918), New York
  - Last Night Came a Host (Provençal Carol, 1570-1610) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    (Arranged for SATB by D.S. Smith)
    Stainer & Bell, Ltd. (1935), 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - Little Jesus (Polish Carol) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    (Arranged by D.S. Smith)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1929), 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - The March of the Three Kings (Old Provençal) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Arranged from Bizet's version by D.S. Smith for SATB
  - Mary's Farewell (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Matin Song Op. 33, No. 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Text: Thomas Heywood (1570-1650)
  - Morning Op. 33, No. 3 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Text: Joanna Baillie (1762-1851)
  - Natal Hymn (à cappella) and Final Chorus, Part IV / From the Christmas Cantata "The Logos" by D.S. Smith (Box 2, Folder 4)
    H.W. Gray Co. (1908), New York
  - No Rest for Thy Head (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1923), 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - Noël Nouvelet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Noel To Honor Mary Mother (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Harmonized for SATB from the version of Léon Roques by D.S. Smith
  - Now All the World Rejoices (Ai! La bonne Fortune), Saboly, Nicolas, 1614-1675 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    French and English Versions by Edward Bliss Reed
  - Now Mary Must Journey (Flemish Carol) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    English Version by Edward Bliss Reed (Arranged by D.S. Smith)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1933) 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - O Nightingale (French Carol) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1925) 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - O Thou Lovely Night (Basque Carol) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1932), 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - Rejoice with Delight (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (192h) 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - Run, Friends, to Greet Him (Provençal Noël 1653-1656) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Stainer and Bell Ltd. (1935) 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - A Saviour For Us Now Is Born (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1924) 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - The Shepherd Boy (Bas Quercy Carol) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Translated by Edward Bliss Read (Arranged by D.S. Smith)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1924), 58, Berners Street, London England
  - The Shepherds (First Melody) Les Bergers, Saboly, Nicolas, 1614-1675 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Sing We Noël Once More (Bas-Quercy Carol) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1923), 58, Berners Street, London England
    (4 copies)
  - Sing We Noël Once More (Bas-Quercy Carol) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Galaxy Music Corporation (1916) (Stainer & Bell Ltd.), 17 West 46th Street, New York
  - Sleep Well, You Heavenly Child (Swiss Carol) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Stainer &. Bell Ltd. (1934), 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - The Sleeping Priestess (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Chorus for Women's Voices and Piano
    Text: Robert Cameron Rogers
    G. Schirmer, Inc. (1910), New York - Boston
  - Susani! Susani! (German Carol, 1623) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ten Provençal Carols, Saboly, Nicolas, 1614-1675 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Set I:
    1. 'Tis the Time for Mirth (Ça! Faisons Rejouissance)
    2. Sing We Noël (Chantons Noël)
    3. You Who Seek to Live in Splendor (Toi qui Cherches tes Délices)
    4. Now all the World Rejoices (Ai! La Bonne Fortune)
    5. Three Wise Men (Les Trois Mages)
    Set II:
    6. The Shepherds (Les Bergers) (G Major)
    7. The Shepherds (Les Bergers) (F Major)
    8. Boots and Saddles (Boute-Selle)
    9. Jesus, You are All Flame (Jésus, Vous êtes Tout Feu)
    10. Touro - Louro - Louro
    Harmonized and Edited by D.S. Smith for SATB and various soloists
    In 2 Volumes
  - There Is No Rose (English Carol XVth Century) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1928), 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - This Is the Time of Joyfulness (English Carol) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Good and True, Fresh and New, Christmas Carols. 1642
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1934), 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - 'Tis the Time for Mirth (Çà! Faisons Réjouissance), Saboly, Nicolas, 1614-1675 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    French and English Version by Edward Bliss Reed
  - To Noel (Poitevin Carol XVth Century) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Arranged for SATB by D.S. Smith
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1926) 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - Touro - Louro - Louro, Saboly, Nicolas, 1614-1675 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Tyrolean Folk Carol (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Wake, Nightingale (Franconian Folk Carol) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - When the Shepherds Knew (Polish Carol) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    English Version by S.L.H. and Edward Bliss Reed (Arranged by D.S. Smith)
    Stainer & Bell Ltd. (1937), 58, Berners Street, London, England
  - You Who Seek to Live in Splendor (Toi qui Cherches tes Délices), Saboly, Nicolas, 1614-1675 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    English and French Version by Edward Bliss Reed
- Richard Stark
  Mus. B. 1951, Mus. M. 1952
  - Praise The Lord (Box 2, Folder 6)
    For Chorus of Mixed Voices (or Chorus of Male or Female Voices) Solo Voice, and Organ
    Text: Psalms 148 (1-3, 7-12) and 150
- Paul Lindsley Thomas
  Mus. B. 1957, Mus. M. 1958
  - Come My Soul (Box 2, Folder 6)
    An Anthem for General Use
    For Mixed Voices SATB with Organ Accompaniment
    Text: F.R.L. von Canitz (1657-1699)
    Translated by Henry J. Buckoll
    Mills Music, Inc. (1961), 1619 Broadway, New York 19, N.Y.
- Francis Thorne
  B.A. 1943
  - Kyrie Eleison, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    SSA à cappella
    Marks Music Corporation (1965), 136 West 52 Street, New York, N.Y. 10019
- Lloyd B. Tuttle
  Mus. B. 1951
  - Let All Men Hear (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Anthem for Men's Voices, TTB
    Text: Rev. Isaac Watts, 1719
    Based on Psalm 78
    H.W. Gray Co. (1960), Near York
- John W. Work
  Mus. B. 1933
  - Go Tell It on The Mountain (Box 2, Folder 7)
    For Chorus of Male Voices Unaccompanied
    Christmas Spiritual Freely arranged by J.W. Work
    Galaxy Music Corporation (1946), 17 West 46th Street, New York
  - Golgotha Is a Mountain (Box 2, Folder 7)
    For Mixed Chorus and Piano or Organ
    Text: Arna Bontemps
    Galaxy Music-Corporation (1959), 2121 Broadway, N.Y. 23, N.Y.
  - Hammering (Box 2, Folder 7)
    For mixed voices à cappella (SATB divided)
    Negro Spiritual Arr. by J.W. Work
    Theodore Presser Co. (1940), 1712 Chestnut Street, Philadelphia, Pa.
  - I Got a House in Baltimore (Box 2, Folder 7)
    For Chorus of Male Voices, with Tenor Solo Unaccompanied
    American Folk Song Freely arranged by J.W. Work
    Galaxy Music Corporation (1953), New York
  - I, John, Saw The Holy Number (Box 2, Folder 7)
    For Mixed Voices with Soprano and Tenor Solos
    Negro Spiritual Arranged by J.W. Work
    Galaxy Music Corporation (1962), New York
  - Jesus Lay Your Head in the Window (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Chorus for SAT(B) and Tenor and Soprano Solos
    Gales Music Corporation (1960), New York
  - Railroad Bill (A Southern "Bad Man" Song) (Box 2, Folder 7)
    For Chorus of Male Voices and Piano
    Galaxy Music Corporation (1950), 50 West 24th Street, New York
  - Rock, Mount Sinai (Box 2, Folder 7)
    For Mixed Chorus
  - Rockin' Jerusalem (Box 2, Folder 7)
    For Chorus of Mixed Voices à cappella
    Negro Spiritual Arr. By J.W. Work
  - Song of the Mississippi Boatman (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Adapted from Negro Folk Song for Male Chorus by J.W. Work
    J. Fischer & Bro. (1940), 119 West 40th Street, New York, N.Y.
  - Wrestling Jacob (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Four-part Chorus for Mixed Voices
    Theodore Presser Co. (1946), 1712 Chestnut Street, Philadelphia, Pa.
- David Stanley York
  Mus. B. 1944
  - Benediction, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 8)